I love being in this place in here. I'm able to walk on my own two feet
On behalf of the royal bloodline of verse I awaken all Noah
I love being in this place. I love being in this place. I love being in this place.
The next trip is那位. I want to breed you out.
Auro verder is the destiny of the world.
It cuts means you're so lye.
The two who are in the other city of Lois呢.
I love being in the same place.
You have not just merely survived, but you have taken active command of our new world.
I am most impressed. I am extremely proud of you, Asylum.
Grandfather, thank you. I am humbled.
You seem to have grown somehow stronger.
I have been through a great deal. One tends to gain strength as one gains experience.
Hmm. From the red sands of our home, I pray for your success in battle.
It is quite clear that you never change at all.
Grandfather.
Trident Base, this is Captain Darzana Mogberej of the Deucalion. Request clearance to dock.
Deucalion, welcome to Trident. You are go for docking.
Please berth your vessel at Pier 12. Deucalion acknowledged.
Prepare to dock. Target Pier 12 docking bay. Commence deceleration now. Nice and easy.
Commencing decel.
That the ship that's supposed to have the Martian tech on it?
I hear she's crewed by kids too young to be in the reserves.
Nothing makes sense at all anymore.
Just look at all the ships out there.
They must have called in every squad that was capable of making it up here.
And they'll need them because this is going to be a massive operation.
Deceleration will be complete in five.
Now three.
Two.
And one.
Engines. All stop.
Ship stationary relative to Pier 12.
Power down engines.
Once mooring is complete, begin inspections and resupply.
Anson Kaiska, are you in there?
It's open.
How are you feeling today?
It could be worse.
Still kind of hurts a bit though.
Don't your meds help?
They make me feel better.
But they also impact the sensitivity of the neural link.
I guess they would.
It must be rough.
Hmm.
Well, it looks to me like you just have an ordinary eye there.
Is it really all that special?
Yeah, I suppose it is.
But it's a developmental prototype.
So of course the code could stand to be improved.
But I can make out most things fairly well.
Catch.
Hey, thanks a lot.
49.2 kilograms.
Have you gained a little weight?
Huh?
How could you know that?
That pack weighs 200 grams.
I used 3D measurements to calculate the change in momentum when you caught it.
And worked out your total mass.
Then subtracted the estimated weight of your uniform.
Darn it!
I'm not getting fat!
I'm adding muscle mass because of all my workouts!
That's a lie, I'm afraid.
I see stress in the formant analysis of your voice.
Oh really?
How do you know it's not broken?
Working perfectly.
What's that?
I've identified similar stress patterns in her voice.
Especially here.
Therefore I, a Salem vs. Ellusia, princess of the Verse Empire.
Now wait a minute here.
If that's a lie, then it means that...
She's not really the princess.
And so you're not telling the truth either, are you?
Have you been stress eating?
I'm not stress eating!
There it goes again.
I'm never gonna speak to you again!
There's something wrong?
No.
Just thinking how easy it was to read Inko.
That clenches it.
You really are.
You're that much of an idiot.
Looks like you're telling the truth.
My lord's lame!
Adele Ritzo, shouldn't you be with Princess Lemarina?
It's all right.
I won't tell anyone.
Sorry, my lord.
Thank you.
Oh, and it seems we have spotted that ship you told us about.
You mean you found the Deucalion?
It looks like they have repaired it.
It defeated Baron Ya'koim and is now in space.
We could be forced to fight with them.
And that would make Princess Asalem very sad.
I can't help wondering when she's going to wake up.
What if she...
If she never does?
Don't you worry.
Have some faith.
We will see her smile again.
I know it.
Oh, m'lady.
I am counting on you
to look after
my Asalem.
Everything is arranged.
Rest assured, Your Majesty.
I once lied to him
that she had been assassinated.
And now I am lying to him
that she is alive.
Tell me something, Slane.
How do you see the state of Verse?
It is not my place to offer opinions
on our sacred homeland.
It is all right.
You may speak freely.
I believe it is possible for our society
in its powerless, impoverished state
to become prosperous by conquering Earth
and taking its resources.
However...
Hmm.
The resources
are likely to find their way
only to the upper class
and will not improve
the lives of the citizens at all.
Then how might we bring about change?
With Alt Noah.
Those who control Alt Noah
control everything.
Fundamentally,
that would be the key.
Very well put.
We owe much to his Imperial Majesty
for bringing Alt Noah's power to light.
But it was a mistake
and a sin
to create a society
where a privileged elite
hoards that power
and controls everything.
Once we have achieved
our righteous victory
and seize the Earth,
that red world
is going to witness change.
I'll need you to lend
your strength, Slane.
I shall, Count Sosbaum.
Are my beloved steeds prepared?
The activation tests
are completed.
Once we fine-tune
the sink between each unit,
they will be combat ready.
Do that when we've
arrived at the base.
Sigus Squadron,
prepare to deploy!
Yes, sir!
Tharsis, stand.
It's not powering up.
The Alt Noah Drive
is offline.
But why?
Princess Lemrina.
Is there something
troubling you, Slane?
Your Highness,
why did you deactivate
the Tharsis?
Whatever do you mean?
You are the only one here
who can forcibly
deactivate Alt Noah.
Quite possibly,
you're right.
Activate the Alt Noah, please.
I will not.
But you must.
You could ask
the other princess.
It always struck me
as odd.
How was it that you,
a Terran,
was able to operate
the Tharsis?
I'm sure she would be
happy to know
how loyal you are,
and that you are
still in love with her
in spite of her
current condition.
It's true we share
the same father,
but I'm only the
afterthought,
because of the simple
fact that we have
different mothers.
That is not the case
at all.
You need to know
that everyone admires
you, Princess Lemrina.
You lie.
It is not a lie.
It is.
You admired
the activation factor,
not me.
Isn't that the reason
you came to me?
Lord Slain.
Do you really want
me that badly?
Or I'll Noah that badly?
Am I just...
the replacement for her?
You can't deny it.
I am that.
You're so shallow.
I hate you.
I was born down there,
on Earth,
and when my scientist
father died on Verse,
I lost my one protector.
I became a servant
to the Verse
Orbital Knights.
I will not say
I understand
your suffering,
but still,
I have known cruelty
due to my birth as well.
I can understand
your pain,
even if only
in some small measure.
So know that you have
my heartfelt admiration,
Princess Lemrina.
Lift your eyes, Slain.
Now go on.
You can activate it.
You have my thanks.
Then good hunting,
Sir Slain Troyart.
My Lord Slain.
My apologies
for causing this delay.
That display was touching.
I am extremely proud
that you are my master.
You saw that then?
Embarrassing.
Launch all units!
Destination
Marinero's base!
Everything that belong to you,
I will now take
for my very own.
So rest easy,
dear sister.
All units,
we will soon
enter Earth orbit.
We will perform
an aerobrake maneuver,
slingshot around the planet,
and enter the satellite belt.
And on to Marinero's base.
My Lord Slain,
it is time.
Right.
Let's go.
As you know,
the countless chunks
of moon rock
that form the satellite belt
travel in an elliptical orbit
around the Earth.
Our Trident base
is located on one.
Now the front line base
of the Martian forces
is Marinero's,
traveling in this orbit.
The two will make
a close approach
in 72 hours' time.
The distance between them
will be a mere
seven kilometers.
Close enough
to be seen
with the naked eye.
A large-scale battle
is expected
between our two bases.
That being the case,
we have gathered
both orbiting
and surface troops
to assemble
the most powerful
fighting force we can.
It is believed
Mars will also be
amassing their forces
for an offensive attack.
Exercise caution
when engaging them.
Mission parameters
We face many challenges
in this war,
but a space battle
on this scale?
Is this something
we can do?
Who knows?
But considering
it's also a first
for the enemy,
it's probably nothing
to worry about.
And yet,
it is still a subject
of great concern.
Such a shame.
If you let that cute,
endearing side of you
show every day,
you'd be more likely
to get a date.
End of deceleration
in five seconds.
Three,
two,
one,
and clear.
We have an opportunity here.
Stygis Squadron,
go and show me
what you're made of.
Stygis once, sir.
As you've commanded.
Stygis two,
as you've commanded.
Stygis three,
High-speed heat signatures
closing in
from low Earth orbit.
Not reading in IFF.
Unidentified.
They're coming from below?
Plot shows them
coming to within
two kilometers of us.
Their trajectory leads
to the Mars Army's
marine aerospace.
Headquarters says
to intercept, ma'am.
The enemy is closing
on the base
at very high speed.
Seven mid-sized ships,
three small units.
A smaller attack
before the main event.
Scramble all
operational shipboard
cataphracts
and ready the ship
for emergency launch.
Com,
is mine ready?
Repairs are done.
We also got it
completely tricked out
for space.
Thanks.
Hey, and are you sure
you want to keep it
that funky orange color?
I can paint it
if you want.
That's okay.
It's supposed to
attract attention.
Huh?
Don't worry about it.
Gennady platoon,
in position.
Haraway platoon,
Mustang,
one-one,
in position.
Mustang,
two-two,
in position.
Relative velocity
continue with the enemy
is three kilometers
per second.
They'll be flashing by.
Meaning their chances
of attacking are slim.
Stygis one here.
Commencing attack.
This is Stygis two.
Stygis three.
Commencing attack.
Heads up!
Incoming!
Bastards!
The gravity flux
is complicated.
Neither of us will land
a hit at this range.
Someone got a hit?
At this range?
Mustang,
zero-zero.
Commencing my attack.
It's Inaho!
Compensating for variable
gravity from satellite debris.
Ready.
Target set.
Fire.
Next one.
And the next.
My lord,
the Stygis squadron.
Carefully, Inaho!
Are you all right,
my lord Sosbom?
Yes, slay.
I will act as a decoy
and draw their fire.
Mr. Harklight,
take evasive action.
Yes, my lord.
They're going to hit.
He dodged it.
How could it have moved
like that?
Pinpoint accuracy.
How are the shots
landing in this flux?
Is it due to speed?
No, not that.
It's predicting the path
of the rounds.
How can it?
Who is this pilot?
It's him.
An orange cataphract?
Can't be.
I've wanted to find you, Bat.
But it looks like
you're a seagull now.
Now look around the world
How can we stop the war?
And you know
that how we...
Enemy convoy
approaching effective
firing range.
Fire at will.
Give him help.
I need to know
that look around the world
So what we're fighting for
Inaho!
I need to know
Enemy convoy has passed.
They're breaking off.
Continue firing
until they're all out of range.
I want a damage report now.
Tharsis.
The personal cataphract
of the orbital knight
Count Cruteo
later owned by
Count Sazbom
but is piloted
by a young knight
under his command.
And the pilot's name
The Orange Cataphract.
It's just a training unit.
Training unit?
Yes, the boy's preference
is only to pilot those.
And the boy?
Yes, my lord.
His name is...
Inaho Kaisuka.
So you're alive.
I found you.
Slain Troiard.
ライクシーン
辛な空を
スタバシ padre
Return to the hand
ウィモリ
公開
僕達は
彷徨ed
未来
入った
戦
壉
天
保
僕達elo
彷徨
卑屈
Oh